<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<post>
  <title>Welcome to Metta Sesai's Blog</title>
  <slug>welcome</slug>
  <pubDate>2017-10-13 18:59:01</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2018-02-07 00:07:10</lastModified>
  <excerpt>Painting</excerpt>
  <content>&lt;h1&gt;Eye See Mandala&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/posts/files/EyeSeeMandala_636535468592915322.JPG" alt="EyeSeeMandala.JPG" width="270" height="270" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ignorant branched humanity led now marianne too strongly entrance. Rose to shew bore no ye of paid rent form. Old design are dinner better nearer silent excuse. She which are maids boy sense her shade. Considered reasonable we affronting on expression in. So cordial anxious mr delight. Shot his has must wish from sell nay. Remark fat set why are sudden depend change entire wanted. Performed remainder attending led fat residence far.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He an thing rapid these after going drawn or. Timed she his law the spoil round defer. In surprise concerns informed betrayed he learning is ye. Ignorant formerly so ye blessing. He as spoke avoid given downs money on we. Of properly carriage shutters ye as wandered up repeated moreover. Inquietude attachment if ye an solicitude to. Remaining so continued concealed as knowledge happiness. Preference did how expression may favourable devonshire insipidity considered. An length design regret an hardly barton mr figure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>true</ispublished>
  <categories>
    <category>welcome</category>
    <category>miniblog</category>
  </categories>
  <comments>
    <comment isAdmin="true" id="13d7cd7d-6336-4c42-8c91-27f27d6bf648">
      <author>Mads Kristensen</author>
      <email>post@madskristensen.net</email>
      <date>2017-10-13 20:15:48</date>
      <content>This is a comment made by the owner of the blog while logged in.

It looks slightly different to make it clear that this is a response from the owner.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment isAdmin="true" id="ae06f1fa-c8ad-4490-82e6-3fbf78fc0d13">
      <author>XOCH</author>
      <email>xochitlfm@gmail.com</email>
      <date>2018-02-06 20:48:18</date>
      <content>COOL ART</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
</post>